MAIN
BEGIN
    CREATE response
    PRINT "It is a dark and stormy night. Do you want to take an umbrella? (Y/N) : "
    response ← READ
    IF (response = "Y")THEN
        PRINT "Good - you have an umbrella."
        IF (secondPrompt = "F")THEN
            PRINT "You take out your umbrella and jab it into the wolf's paw! It runs away and you live another day."
        ELSE
            PRINT "You begin running so fast, the umbrella opens and you fly away like Mary Poppins.You're a little embarrassed, but you see the wolf fading off in the distance."
        ENDIF
    ELSE
        PRINT "You decide not to take an umbrella."
        IF (secondPrompt = "F")THEN
            PRINT "You begin fighting the wolf only to realize you had just eaten a McGrease® meal earlier.You fall dead from rigorous exercise, having had a heart attack."
        ELSE
            PRINT "Are you serious? You can't outrun a wolf! The wolf catches you and you are somewhat relieved because you don't have to worry about that Calculus exam…"
        ENDIF
    ENDIF
END MAIN

METHOD secondPrompt ()
BEGIN
    CREATE response
    PRINTLINE
    PRINT "You start to walk down a path and hear a scream. You realize that the person screaming is YOU because you see a wolf! Do you fight with your umbrella or run ? ((F)ight / (R)un) : "
    response ← READ
    PRINTLINE
    return response
END secondPrompt